freshtunes.com 2019-10-16

# Freshtunes

FreshTunes FZ-LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. This policy (together with the Terms and Conditions) explains how FreshTunes will process, use or share any personal data it collects from you, or that you provide to FreshTunes. By visiting and using FreshTunes’ website: [freshtunes.com](https://freshtunes.com/), any associated digital app which FreshTunes may release from time to time, and any related properties (the “Service”), you are accepting and consenting to this policy. FreshTunes may, from time to time, make changes to its privacy policy and these will be posted on this page. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to the FreshTunes privacy policy. FreshTunes’ privacy policy was last updated on 16.02.2017

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), FreshTunes is the data controller and FreshTunes will only use the information that it collects about you lawfully (in accordance with the Act).

Please read this policy in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions. Any capitalised terms used but not defined in this policy shall have the meanings given to them in the Terms and Conditions.

The Service may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of its partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that FreshTunes does not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

#### Information FreshTunes may collect

FreshTunes may collect and process information about you when you use the Service. In particular, this may include information you give FreshTunes by filling in forms on the Service or by corresponding with FreshTunes, including when you register to use the Service or upload Content. The information you give FreshTunes may include (without limitation) your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and personal description. All credit card information is entered into the WebMoney or PayPal payment system and FreshTunes does not see or keep these details.

FreshTunes may also automatically gather information on how you use FreshTunes’ Service to help FreshTunes develop and improve its Service and to provide relevant, helpful information to you. This includes information about your device such as domain name, browser type and version, operating system, IP address, cookie information, time stamp, what web pages you visit on FreshTunes’ website, and how long you spend on each page. FreshTunes do not gather information about other third party websites you have visited.

FreshTunes may also collect data on the Content you upload to the Service to enable FreshTunes to upload the Content to its website and to create a personal web page for you. The content may comprise of the Recordings, Metadata and Artwork.

FreshTunes also works closely with third parties (such as sub-contractors in payment and delivery services, digital music service providers and online retailers) in order to give you the best experience possible and FreshTunes may receive information about you from them.

#### Using your information

Collection of your information helps us better understand what you need from FreshTunes and its Service. The main uses of your personal information are:

  * To register you to use the Service;
  * To contact you to deliver certain services or information you have requested;
  * To verify your authority to receive information or to use the Service;
  * To improve the content and general administration of FreshTunes’ website and Service; and
  * To provide you with notices regarding FreshTunes’ Service, and, with your permission, provide updates and information about FreshTunes and its Service.

When you subscribe to the Service, FreshTunes will use your information for the performance of the Service. This may include disclosing your data to digital music service providers, online retailers and sub-contractors necessary for the processing and performance of the Service.

FreshTunes may use the information you provide and the information FreshTunes receives from third parties to carry out FreshTunes’ obligations and to provide you with the information, content, services and products that you request from FreshTunes and to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about other content, goods and services which FreshTunes feels may interest you. FreshTunes will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if FreshTunes intends to use your data for marketing purposes or if FreshTunes intends to disclose your information to third parties for such purposes. You have the right to ask FreshTunes not to process your personal data for marketing purposes and you will have the opportunity to refuse any such marketing correspondence from FreshTunes or third parties by checking certain boxes on the forms FreshTunes uses to collect your personal data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at: [support@freshtunes.com](mailto:support@freshtunes.com).

FreshTunes may also use the information FreshTunes collects about you to administer and improve the Service and to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising FreshTunes serves you, and to deliver personalised services and relevant or targeted advertising to you.

#### Disclosing your information

FreshTunes may disclose your personal information to third parties in the event that FreshTunes sells or buys any business or assets, in which case FreshTunes may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer, or where FreshTunes is under a duty to do so in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply FreshTunes’ Terms and Conditions and other agreements or to protect FreshTunes’ customers or others.

FreshTunes may also share your information with selected third parties including affiliated partners, Distribution Network partners, Exclusive Distribution Network partners, providers, retailers advertisers, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract FreshTunes enters into with them or you or the performance of any order you place through the Service.

#### Information you share with other users

You may voluntarily share information, data and other content with other users via the Service. Please be careful about disclosing any information or content that includes sensitive details about you such as your religious beliefs, sexual orientation, ethnic background and health details. While you may voluntarily upload information of this type, please be aware that any content you post via the Service may reveal these kinds of sensitive personal data to other users (and the public at large). Where you do upload information and content of this nature, you are explicitly consenting to FreshTunes processing this information and making it available to other users.

When you share information or Content on the Service, the amount of personal information you share about yourself or others is at your own risk. Any information or Content you upload to the Service will be available to other users of the Service and other users of the Distribution Networks and Exclusive Network. FreshTunes is not responsible for the Content you choose to share via the Service and you must obtain the consent of any person that features or is referred to in your Content.

By using the Service, you agree that FreshTunes may (but is not obliged to) moderate the Content you share to ensure it complies with this policy and the Terms and Conditions.

FreshTunes will cooperate with all law enforcement enquiries and third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights. FreshTunes may also access and disclose your personal information and content to government or law enforcement agencies or courts as required by law or, in FreshTunes’ sole discretion, when FreshTunes believes that disclosure is necessary to protect itself, you or any third parties.

#### Storing your information

The data and information that FreshTunes collects from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for FreshTunes or for one of FreshTunes’ suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. FreshTunes will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Where FreshTunes provides you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the Service, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. Please do not share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. FreshTunes cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Service; any transmission is at your own risk.

#### Access to information

You can check the information that FreshTunes holds about you by emailing FreshTunes at [support@freshtunes.com](mailto:support@freshtunes.com) and FreshTunes will amend any inaccuracies promptly. Any such request to access the information FreshTunes holds about you may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet FreshTunes’ costs in providing you with the details of such information. FreshTunes may also ask you for a copy of you ID to make sure FreshTunes is sending the information to the right person.

#### Cookies

The Service uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of the Service and to improve your overall experience. When you use the Service, certain information may be stored locally on your device using 'cookies' or similar technologies such as objects stored in the device’s local storage. A cookie is a small text file used to store limited information about the user of the device. They help FreshTunes to identify how FreshTunes’ users use the Service, and so that FreshTunes can continue to develop and improve it.

Cookies do this by storing information about your preferences on your device, including the device model, manufacturer, screen resolution, device capabilities, service provider, country and city location data.

FreshTunes accesses this information when you use the Service, to provide you with content, in accordance with the rights FreshTunes have licensed, which is more relevant to your individual interests and for reporting and analytics purposes.

Specifically, the cookies FreshTunes use help FreshTunes to:

  * Estimate the number of visitors to FreshTunes’ website and usage patterns so that FreshTunes can understand how its website is used and how FreshTunes can improve visitors’ experiences;
  * Store information about your preferences and to therefore allow FreshTunes to customise its website according to individual interests; and
  * To recognise you when you return to the website.

FreshTunes use the following types of cookies:

  * Strictly necessary: These cookies enable FreshTunes’ Service to function correctly and deliver the services and products visitors have requested.
  * Performance & Functionality: These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of FreshTunes’ Service but are non-essential to their use (for example, FreshTunes use cookies to remember your preferences on the Service). However, without these cookies, certain functionality (like videos and survey functionality) may become unavailable.
  * Analytical: These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help FreshTunes understand how the Service is being used or how effective FreshTunes’ marketing campaigns are, so FreshTunes can research the usability of its Service, or to help FreshTunes customise the Service for you. In particular FreshTunes use the Google analytics cookies. For more information about Google’s privacy policy, please visit http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/. If you do not wish to allow the use of Google Analytics cookies at all, Google provides an opt-out plug-in for most common website browsers http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
  * User Authentication: These cookies are used to enable you to share pages and content that you find interesting on the Service through third party social networking websites.

By using the Service, you accept the use of cookies in accordance with this privacy policy.

 **Your cookie choices**

You have the right to choose whether to accept or refuse cookies and similar technologies. You can exercise this choice by not accepting the Terms and Conditions and this privacy policy, however, please note that if you choose to do so, you will not be able to use the Service.

For more information about what cookies are and your rights to control cookies, please visit the third party educational resource www.allaboutcookies.org.

#### Disclosing personal details

FreshTunes will not ask you for credit card details or other security passwords in unsolicited phone calls or emails. If you receive such a request, please report it to FreshTunes by emailing: [support@freshtunes.com](mailto:support@freshtunes.com)

#### How to contact FreshTunes and further information

The Service is offered by FreshTunes FZ-LLC trading as FreshTunes. FreshTunes is incorporated under the laws of the United Arab Emirates. FreshTunes' registered address is: Executive Office #20, Floor: 07, Building Aurora Tower, Dubai, United Arab Emirates.

If you have any feedback, questions or complaints about this privacy policy or any requests for technical support, then please refer to FreshTunes’ FAQ page or contact FreshTunes by sending an email to: [support@freshtunes.com](mailto:support@freshtunes.com)
